[Music]
welcome to busy Central lunch event
20125 release wave one in this session
we will show the most of our new
enhancements related to eents in this
wave before we go to all these new
features I want to remind you on our e
doent solution Journey why I'm doing
that because I want to remind you that
we start with this project just two
years ago only two years ago and when
say two years we didn't deliver first
release our idea is 2 years old our
internal project kickoff uh happened May
2023 so in first wave wave two Tober
2023 we just deliver some basic set of
functionality we made localization for
Denmark first connectors and just F yes
in first uh interface for extending then
we added
more features we added uh we got first
users and partners uh added some new
localizations we added Co pilot then we
continue with
um attachments to P format with some new
uh different formats and different uh
connectors then slightly we move to New
localization end of last year with
Germany and Spanish localization and so
on so on so now we are in 20 25 release
way one you will see many new features
so I will not read all of them in this
moment and what is important you can
expect much more to come in next miners
we are expecting new eents apis some new
document types so we are Contin to
invest in uh this module so this is
important for Microsoft and we will
continue to invest based on your
feedback and what we see as strategical
moves so we already have backlog for
next wave so you can expect much more
more good new things in October so let's
make an overview of what is new and you
will see this is a full screen of all
new features and I'm pretty sure now if
I calculate that more than 50% are based
on your feedback so this is important
every time when you have feedback tell
us and we will try to improve uh this
module based on that so now we have
possibility to delete incorrect e
documents and avoid duplicates this this
was important because in some cases you
could uh repeat
um um entering the same type of document
so system will now if recognize this
duplicate just remove automatically so
now Additionally you can send e
documents via service and email
simultaneously so this is important very
often even even if you have some service
some connector you want to send to some
specific person via email this document
so now you can do it in a parallel then
multiple incoming documents can be
attached if you remember if you're
working manually you could attach only
one by one now you can set all of them 5
6 10 and attach automatically then the
uh automated attachments into P format
so now if you're working sales system
will automatically take your uh invoice
uh uh layout and attach to your
documents and send this automatically
when we receive system will
automatically extract your PDF from um
uh payal and you will see this uh PDF
into f f box in electronic document so
there are so many new things
uh process documents in two steps uh
preview incoming um uh electronic
invoices uh export reminders Finance
charart the PayPal files and fix
unposted purchase document because what
could happen you could have accidentally
to delete uh purchase invoice already
connected electronic invoice or purchase
crit memo now you can just go back to
electronic uh document and you can say
uh recreate and system will
automatically recreate purchase invoice
and purch create member so many new
interesting things new connectors uh new
localizations new interface so many new
things and I would like now to emphasize
uh this one Asia docum intelligence f e
documents and why I will move to this
story shortly to explain why this is
important what we had earlier electronic
invoice so this is some XML format the
most of these formats for XML type it
doesn't mean they're NE to be XML but
electronic documents some kind of
machine readable format as electronic
inv voice we got this as this is machine
readable format we created our our
electronic document in a busy Central if
we had this format already set up so it
was how system worked earlier and how it
still work but what we added now you can
get even PDF invoice and why this is
important maybe you are in country where
you have enforcement to use electronic
invoices but you will still have vendors
from some other countries and if this
other countries it doesn't mean that
they have enforcement to use electronic
invoices and you can get PDF so our idea
is to keep the same user experience so
you do not need to switch from one
functionality to another absolutely
everything the same so now if you
receive PDF invoice system will send to
Asia document intelligence and what it
is actually this is OCR service our Asia
OCR service now embedded in a busy
Central so syst will send to asure
document intelligence when we get uh
information back it will be again
machine aable format from this moment
when this is machine aable format there
is no any difference if this original
document was from PDF or from XML or
some other format this is Mas format we
will proceed electronic documents and
proceed um uh further creating purchase
invoices purchase create mem whatever
you got so this is important now um I
want to emphasize this is still work in
progress we have this in the preview uh
but this is something what will come
very soon and we will have separate
session about uh showing all these
details related to PDF so in this
session we will not show this part I
just wanted to emphasize that this is
now unique platform so whatever you are
working if you're working only
electronic invoices good if you're
working only with PDFs good if you have
combination everything good the same use
experience so this is the main message
you will have the same user experience
and all features already existing for
electronic invoicing for example
co-pilot for matching with purchase
order it can be used with PDF invoices
as well and opposite everything what is
created for PDF can be used for
electronic invoices so this is the main
message uh about that but now I will uh
switch to my colleague Magnus and he
will show the most attractive definitely
we cannot show all these features and
yes before we switch to Magnus some of
these features will be available in
April some of them will be available in
May or June but this is the least of
features what you can expect in April or
very soon after that so Magnus please
show us some of these exciting
features thanks Alexander yeah so I
picked out uh a handful of them to uh to
demo today so we can see how they are in
the product so let's start with the
two-step processing so I will show you
that on our e doent Services
page we now have this new field called
automatic processing and as Alexander
said before this release this was always
uh true we would always try uh and
create a purchase invoice but again with
feedback from the community from our
users and our partners there was a
request to actually being able to review
uh the document before you you go ahead
and create uh the the purchase invoice
in BC so let us demonstrate that so I
will go ahead and uh and set this to
know for my service and then I will
navigate to our e doents list page to
demo uh importing a document and here
you can see actually that uh for today's
uh illustration purposes I have a e
document that is uh in an error State uh
and one of the the new things that we
also can do is that we can now delete
eents if they are wrong or if the
received content is not what was agreed
upon and so on so there is this option
now so this one I actually want to get
rid of so I will just go ahead and
delete
it click yes and we of course make sure
that that when you delete that you
actually want to delete it because you
might not be able to retrieve it again
especially if it's coming from an
external service so but in this case I
want to so I'll go ahead and click yes
and then I will upload a
new file
here I will choose my demo
XML and as you can see it opens up the E
doent and and it has been what I guess
we can consider partially processed we
can inspect the preview lines here to
see that okay there is a desk in this uh
invoice uh it has there is only one of
them and it has a certain
price before we actually go ahead and
create the purchase invoice you can go
and see the lines again you can go under
related view extracted data to to also
inspect Header information that will
eventually end up on the uh created
purchase invoice in BC
so this looks good to me I'll just do a
final confirmation with the attachment
that we now automatically attaches any
embedded uh PDF in the XML so I can open
up and see uh that this was provided
with the E invoice and to me I'll zoom
in a little bit here it looks okay so I
am good to go ahead and actually process
the document so I'll click reprocess
document and now we have uh the the
invoice here we can see that it was
filled out and I will open it
up and we now have a uh a created
purchase invoice and this is how you can
now do two-step processing uh when you
have this field set to know in the E
doent
service then also just to illustrate the
deletion for a more realistic scenario I
will upload another
file demo one
here and again we have it in this uh in
this uh draft after or in this in
between before we have created the the
purchase invoice in the system and I
actually don't I don't agree with the
with what it was it was not what uh we
want to create an invoice with so I'll
go ahead and I will just click the the
delete um and again we'll make sure that
you actually want to go ahead and do
this and then you click yes and it will
delete the
document then I will actually switch to
the sending side to demo another new
addition namely uh embedding the invoice
that you are sending in the XML when
you're sending it off so that the
receiver will get a a printed version
and if they're using BC it will be in
the fact box in their incoming e doent
so let's see how that works so on my
demo sending company here I will open up
e doent Services because this also a
configuration you will need to set so
I'll open up my pagero connector
and I will scroll down to the exporting
Tab and here we can see we have a new
parameter embed document PDF to export
and I will actually enable this so now
whenever I create a e doent when posting
I will embed that PDF of that invoice
inside the XML so let's try and do that
so I'll go to One customer 1000 here I
will create a new sales
invoice and then I'll just quickly fill
it out with
uh one of desk here that is fine and I
will just put a test reference in this
one let's see it is fine release and
post
here and then I will open up the posted
invise and as you've could you can just
go to related e documents and then open
up the related document to this posted
sales
invoice and now it gets a little bit uh
gnly you have to go under the locks
because we to inspect the XML so we can
see that that the embedded PDF is
actually there so I'll open up the locks
in the new uh fact box here see that we
have our exported lock from here we can
export the file and I will just open it
up quickly and zoom in a little bit and
you can see here under in the purle
standard this is what we have added that
under attachments we now have that uh
that is an embedded binary object that
contains that invoice um that you posted
and that's uh yeah that is a a brief
look into some of the the things that we
have shipped and uh yeah back to you
Alexander thank you
Magnus as I told in the beginning and
there are so many new exciting features
it will take much more time to go deep
in all of them but please uh some other
uh yes features are explaining some
other sessions so I'm inviting you to
watch another session because in this
release in this busy cental launch event
we will have six different sessions
related to electronic uh documents so
please watch one of them because we'll
find many many exciting new features so
now thank you for watching this video